http://www.webdivisor.com/privacypolicy.aspx

destination:
Privacy Policy
You can rest assure knowing that your privacy is protected and taken seriously here at WebDivisor.
Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.
Policy Details : Privacy Policy
What information does WebDivisor gather?
When you use WebDivisor's services, WebDivisor will obtain specific contact information, such as first name, last name, street address, city, state/province, zip/postal code, country, e-mail address, phone number, fax number, organization name, as well as payment information, such as first name, last name, street address, zip/postal code, credit card number, credit card expiration date.
WebDivisor will also track your session and usage behavior throughout our web site, such as date and times of use, your specific internet address assigned to you, and pages you may have visited on our web site.
WebDivisor will also track requests you make in regards to our products and services and any other feedback that you may provide us.
Finally, WebDivisor keeps records of your payment history and any communications that you may have had with WebDivisor; except in any extraordinary circumstances such as court order to protect the company's rights or property, or in emergencies when someone's safety is at risk.
What does WebDivisor do with this information?
WebDivisor uses the information gathered in order to provide you with the best online experience possible.
Your contact information is used primarily for the purpose of contacting you in regards to your account and our company.
Your payment information is used to validate your identity as well as to bill you for your products and services with WebDivisor.
Your session is primarily tracked for the purpose of allocating system resources appropriately and providing you with service better suited for your needs.
All other communications are tracked for the primary purpose of evaluation and quality assurance.
In addition, WebDivisor regularly sends out mailings regarding the operation of its services and other products that may be of interest to you.
You may disable this option by logging into your account and disabling all or some of your system notification preferences.
WebDivisor reserves the right to send bulletins and other important information regarding its services at its discretion.
Does WebDivisor share subscriber information with third parties?
WebDivisor will not share or disclose information regarding its subscribers except during any legal processes such as court order; when reasonably necessary to protect the company's rights or property; in emergencies where someone's safety is at risk; or as required for domain name registrations.
You should be aware that any information that you disclose in a public space such as a chat room, bulletin board, personal web site, or domain registration lookup (WhoIS) are freely available to anyone else visiting that space.
WebDivisor cannot safeguard any personally identifiable information that you disclose in these locations, nor can it ensure that information you voluntarily supply to third parties remains private.
Please review privacy policies of third party sites you frequently use to ensure that your privacy preferences are respected.
Security
The security of your personal information is very important to us here at WebDivisor.
We will encrypt any sensitive information (such as your credit card number) that you input through our order form or via member services using secure socket layer technology (SSL).
Any information believed to be sensitive such as your credit card number will be stored in an encrypted format to further enhance the type of protection we provide.
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we have received it.
No method of transmission over the internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure.
Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
How can I correct or update the information?
You may update your contact information associated with your account via our member services area.
Please keep in mind that under WebDivisor's terms of service agreement, subscribers are required to provide WebDivisor with current contact and billing information.
WebDivisor may require a copy of a government issued form of identification before disclosing billing or contact information to end users who are unable to access their account due to outdated e-mail addresses; at which point they are unable to reset their account password.
What happens to the information if I leave WebDivisor?
If you ever cancel all of your services with WebDivisor, WebDivisor will normally delete your personally identifiable account information within twelve months after your account is cancelled, unless we are under legal obligation to retain the information.
We preserve your account information for the short period of time in the event that you decide to reactivate your account.
However, in the event of accounting irregularities, WebDivisor reserves the right to retain your contact and billing information as necessary to resolve these matters.
Policy Changes & Questions
WebDivisor reserves the right to make changes to this policy.
Minor changes will become effective immediately upon posting them to this privacy statement.
However, major changes will become effective 30 days after they are posted in this privacy policy or they will be e-mailed to you with an appropriate effective time frame.
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please send us an e-mail by clicking here.
Return to our home page...
Copyright © 2000-2010 WebDivisor. All Rights Reserved.
Terms of Service. Privacy Policy. Guarantees. Affiliates. Site Map.
